<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Powershell on Fletcher&#39;s Cloud Journey</title>
    <link>https://cloud.fskelly.com/tags/powershell/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Powershell on Fletcher&#39;s Cloud Journey</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 11:14:30 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cloud.fskelly.com/tags/powershell/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Check Powershell Console Type</title>
      <link>https://cloud.fskelly.com/post/2022/check-powershell-type/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 11:14:30 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloud.fskelly.com/post/2022/check-powershell-type/</guid>
      <description>I have been working with some Microsoft Hybrid technologies. My specific example here is around Azure Arc-enabled VMware vSphere aspects. When running the scripts provided here there is a key aspect.
Do NOT run this in the PowerShell ISE.
Even with this strong recommendation, it is often accidentally used as it is really easy to perform this action with a right click option and this got me to thinking about how can I check this via code?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using SSH Keys with Bicep based Linux VM templates</title>
      <link>https://cloud.fskelly.com/post/2022/bicep-linux-vm-ssh-keys/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 08:54:21 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloud.fskelly.com/post/2022/bicep-linux-vm-ssh-keys/</guid>
      <description>I this post, I use bicep files for the deployment of Linux VMs AND I add some magic with PowerSehll to allow for the creation or using of existing SSH keys with these VMs.
I am a HUGE fan of SSH keys with Linux VMs for obvious reasons. I could just not find a script or scenario that covered this topic in a way that I actually like. I like to show more details and explain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Openssh and creating SSH Keys with Powershell</title>
      <link>https://cloud.fskelly.com/post/2022/openssh-powershell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 14:27:03 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloud.fskelly.com/post/2022/openssh-powershell/</guid>
      <description>In this post I show you my process for creating SSH Keys for Linux Machines.
I use a fair amount of Linux in my work career (creating VMs and the like within Azure). Linux VMs are great for testing with, they use SSH and are configured and ready for testing VERY quickly in Azure. I also use a fair amount of Linux in personal life, with Home assistant and Plex.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
