<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Identity on Fletcher&#39;s Cloud Journey</title>
    <link>https://cloud.fskelly.com/tags/identity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Identity on Fletcher&#39;s Cloud Journey</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 09:39:57 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cloud.fskelly.com/tags/identity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New LDAPS run-command for Azure VMware Solution</title>
      <link>https://cloud.fskelly.com/post/2023/avs-new-ldaps-run-command/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 09:39:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloud.fskelly.com/post/2023/avs-new-ldaps-run-command/</guid>
      <description>What are we doing? Showing a newer version of the New-LdapsIDentitySource Run-Command within Azure VMware Solution
Lets build this If you have been following along and you have used our previous article(s) - AZURE VMWARE SOLUTION: A COMPREHENSIVE GUIDE TO LDAPS IDENTITY INTEGRATION - PART 1 - you would have realized that this quite a process. We took our many customers feedback to our Product Group (PG) within Microsoft and we have worked with them, to create a new version of the &amp;ldquo;Run-Command&amp;rdquo; and this has been released publicly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azure VMware Solution: A comprehensive guide to LDAPS identity integration - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://cloud.fskelly.com/post/2023/avs-ldaps-configure-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 08:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloud.fskelly.com/post/2023/avs-ldaps-configure-part1/</guid>
      <description>Author(s): Robin Heringa and Fletcher Kelly
Implementing LDAPS identity integration with Azure VMware Solution series - 1 of 4 This is the first part of the blog series on how to implement LDAPS identity integration with Azure VMware Solution. Other parts of this series can be found here:
LDAPS integration - part 2 of 4 LDAPS integration - part 3 of 4 LDAPS integration - part 4 of 4 Azure VMware Solution (AVS) offers a fully managed software defined data center based on VMware vSphere technologies in the shape of an Azure PaaS service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azure VMware Solution: A comprehensive guide to LDAPS identity integration - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://cloud.fskelly.com/post/2023/avs-ldaps-configure-part2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 08:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloud.fskelly.com/post/2023/avs-ldaps-configure-part2/</guid>
      <description>Author(s): Robin Heringa and Fletcher Kelly
Implementing LDAPS identity integration with Azure VMware Solution series - 2 of 4 This is the second part of the blog series on how to implement LDAPS identity integration with Azure VMware Solution. Other parts of this series can be found here:
LDAPS integration - part 1 of 4 LDAPS integration - part 3 of 4 LDAPS integration - part 4 of 4 Configure DNS forwarding prerequisite Before we can configure integration with an external identity store (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azure VMware Solution: A comprehensive guide to LDAPS identity integration - Part 3</title>
      <link>https://cloud.fskelly.com/post/2023/avs-ldaps-configure-part3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 08:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloud.fskelly.com/post/2023/avs-ldaps-configure-part3/</guid>
      <description>Author(s): Robin Heringa and Fletcher Kelly
Implementing LDAPS identity integration with Azure VMware Solution series - 3 of 4 This is the third part of the blog series on how to implement LDAPS identity integration with Azure VMware Solution. Other parts of this series can be found here:
LDAPS integration - part 1 of 4 LDAPS integration - part 2 of 4 LDAPS integration - part 4 of 4 Implement LDAPS integration The following sections will guide you through the required process step-by-step</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Azure VMware Solution: A comprehensive guide to LDAPS identity integration - Part 4</title>
      <link>https://cloud.fskelly.com/post/2023/avs-ldaps-configure-part4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 08:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloud.fskelly.com/post/2023/avs-ldaps-configure-part4/</guid>
      <description>Author(s): Robin Heringa and Fletcher Kelly
Implementing LDAPS identity integration with Azure VMware Solution series - 4 of 4 This is the fourth and final part of the blog series on how to implement LDAPS identity integration with Azure VMware Solution. Other parts of this series can be found here:
LDAPS integration - part 1 of 4 LDAPS integration - part 2 of 4 LDAPS integration - part 3 of 4 These steps, for now, are run manually from the Azure Portal.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
